<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Covid-19 Checkup</string>
    <string name="start">Start</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="good_morning_fullname">Hello,</string>
    <string name="how_are_you_feeling_today">How Are You Feeling Today?</string>
    <string name="statistcs">Statistcs</string>
    <string name="statiscs_details" >The coronavirus COVID-19 is affecting 223 countries and territories. The day is reset after midnight GMT+0. The list of countries and their regional classification is based on the United Nations Geoscheme.</string>
    <string name="show">Show</string>
    <string name="self_checker">Self-Checker</string>
    <string name="the_coronav">The Coronavirus Self-Checker is an interactive clinical assessment tool that will assist individuals ages 13 and older, and parents and caregivers of children ages 2 to 12 on deciding when to seek testing or medical care if they suspect they or someone they know has contracted COVID-19 or has come into close contact with someone who has COVID-19.</string>
    <string name="let_s_check_up">Let\'s Check Up</string>
    <string name="stay_at_home_nsave_yourself_and_the_world">Stay At Home!\nSave Yourself and the World.</string>
    <string name="stay_at_home_desc">Get the latest case data and updates, learn how to protect yourself and others and get advice on what to do next if you think you might have COVID-19.</string>
    <string name="symptoms">Symptoms</string>
    <string name="symptoms_desc">COVID-19 affects different people in different ways. Most people who develop it have mild to moderate symptoms and recover without hospitalization.</string>
    <string name="news">NEWS</string>
    <string name="how_covid_19_spread">How COVID-19 Spread</string>
    <string name="someone_sneezing_next_to_you">Someone Sneezing Next To You</string>
    <string name="the_truth_is">The truth is the virus can land on surfaces when someone coughs or sneezes, ” Dr. Saunders notes. “And if you touch that surface with your hands and then touch your eyes, mouth or nose, you can still contract the virus and become sick.</string>
    <string name="communicating_with">Communicating With An Infected \nPerson</string>
    <string name="contact_with">Contact With Surfaces Carrying\nThe Virus</string>
</resources>